You kick them out?
Yeah, the guys we don't need in our guild.
A lot of guilds have been doing it lately.
Maybe we should, too.
Do it, Mister Guildmaster
of the Beast's Fangs.
Kicking people out is great.
Your personnel expenses go down,
and you don't have to look at
their stupid faces anymore.
All right!
Then I'll kick someone out, too!
That was a lot of work.
Another successful monster-slaying quest.
You guys are back already?
All we found were weaklings.
They're so lucky they get to fight.
I've never fought before.
I've focused on enhancing
weapons and equipment
as an enchanter during
my time with the guild.
Hey, Rein. Quit looking around
the room and do your job.
Right, sorry.
This ain't bad at all.
With your enchantments, even an ordinary
sword becomes a legendary blade.
Right?
Oh, right.
Rein, Barrius wanted to see you. Let's go.
The guildmaster?
That shield. That sword.
That armor. That axe.
I enchanted all of them.
I may not go into battle, but I
contribute to everyone's achievements.
The guildmaster is asking for me.
I wonder what it's about.
Will I get a raise? Or maybe...
an adventurer traveled from far away to
ask me to enchant something for them?
You're fired.
With all the powerful weapons and armor
we have, we don't need you anymore.
All you can do is enchant items.
You can't even fight.
So naturally, you're fired.
Seriously? That doesn't make any sense!
You're fired.
Come on, you heard him.
Get out of here, useless.
I still haven't accepted this!
That's not our problem.
You wanna fight?! Huh?!
Ow...
I may be inexperienced, but that doesn't
mean I can't become an adventurer.
Shut up, Rein!
You can't do it!
Nobody wants to adventure with you!
You're just an enchanting one-trick pony!
All our gear's already enchanted!
Of course you're getting cut!
Quit staring, jerk!
Get out of here, loser!
Incompetent!
Go die on the street!
Get outta here!
I thought they were my friends.
Nobody's going to save me?
Well, I've had enough
of this shitty guild!
THE LAID-OFF CHEAT-GRANTING MAGE
ENJOYS A SECOND LEASE ON LIFE
Where am I?
What am I even saying?
There's no point in moping forever.
If they're going to do whatever
they want, then I will, too.
The enchantments I cast
enhance weapons and armor
by imbuing them with bonus points,
a special type of mana.
And...
Dispel all the enchantments I cast
on the weapons and armor of the
512 members of the Beast's Fangs.
I can take back the points I've granted.
These are all bonus points
I gave to everyone else.
I can't leave them like this.
I need to put them in something.
This is all I've got on me.
COPPER SWORD (CHEAP)
Okay, let's test it.
I still have 3,033 points left.
Then this is a Copper Sword +10,000.
What should I put points into next?
Armor or a shield?
But I don't have either.
There.
Plain Clothes +3,033.
I bet they offer more protection
than standard armor now.
I've enhanced my sword and clothes.
I may be inexperienced, but I should
be able to fight with just these.
I've never taken a break
from working until now.
I always wanted to take it
easy and try adventuring, too.
I could do both now.
I'll earn money adventuring for a guild
and then enjoy my freedom!
EVERYONE KNOWS WHAT IT'S LIKE WHEN NOTHING GOES
RIGHT, BUT WHAT DO I DO WHEN THAT HAPPENS?
WHY, IT'S OBVIOUS! I RUN AND SCREAM MY HEAD OFF!
KINGDOM OF ZELUGE
Excuse me.
I'm looking for an adventurer's
guild other than the Beast's Fangs.
This is a bakery.
At least buy something.
Okay, I'll take a croissant.
So, know any guilds?
Can't say I do.
You have a question? Buy something first.
I'll tell you if you buy something.
Buy a mask.
I'm having trouble finding anything.
Hey, you.
Who, me?
Yeah, you.
Who else do you see?
Your money.
Hand it over.
Your equipment and physique
don't look like much.
You don't wanna get slugged in the
stomach, do you? Hand it over.
I'm wearing enhanced clothes.
I doubt a punch to the
stomach would hurt at all.
I want to test the defense
of my Plain Clothes +3,033!
Hey!
What do you two think you're doing?!
Huh?
Who the hell are you?
It doesn't matter who I am.
Your behavior is the bigger problem.
What? We're just talking to our friend.
I-In any case, I'm calling for help.
What was that, bitch?
You wanna get beaten first?
Wait.
You're dealing with me.
Thanks for the help, but step back.
I want to get punched in
the stomach right now!
What is he saying?
Wait, that'll hurt a lot! Don't do it!
Shut up! Just let me let them punch me!
Let you let them... What are you saying?!
You wanna get punched
in the stomach, huh?!
It doesn't hurt.
Ow! That's hard as hell!
AAAAAUGH
Why are you horrified, too?!
You'll pay for this, brat!
We'll get you!
Do you have a metal plate under there?
I enhanced my clothes
with 3,033 bonus points.
Yeah, yeah. A likely story.
Are you an adventurer?
Yeah. I'm Rein.
I'm Nina.
By the way, Nina, are there any
adventurer's guilds around here?
You're looking for a guild?
Then why not join the Blue Crystals?
I've never heard of them.
Are they really from around here?
Yes, we are! I'm a receptionist
for the Blue Crystals!
If you'd like, I can go with you.
I'm on my way back right now.
I see. In that case, lead the way.
Try not to be surprised, though.
By what?
You'll see when we get there.
DECREPIT
Disappointed? Changed your
mind about joining us?
No, Nina. I'll register
as an adventurer here.
What?! Really?!
Yeah.
You'll register as an adventurer with us?!
I already said I would!
Master, big news!
Someone would like to
register with the guild!
What?! No way!
Are you sure it's not the usual,
"This isn't the Beast's Fangs?
You're a different guild? Never mind,"
and then they leave?
I want to join your guild
because I left the Beast's Fangs.
Yes! Nice work, Nina!
I'm Elsie, guildmaster
of the Blue Crystals.
Nice to meet you.
Yo.
Well, I'll be working in the back.
If you need anything,
don't hesitate to ask.
Elsie is happy to lend an ear anytime.
Take care of the rest, Nina.
Okay.
That's all on intermediary
fees and rewards.
Sign here, and you'll be
registered as an adventurer.
Got it.
Wait, this isn't the Beast's Fangs?
Of course it isn't.
Just look at this dump.
Hey!
We'll let you choose. Hand over your
money, or we'll destroy the place.
Wh-What?
The job we accepted here
the other day was awful.
We'll forgive you if you pay us.
Or you can hand that guy over.
Let's do that.
Okay, step outside.
Sure.
Wait, Rein!
What are you going to do?
They seem to have business with me.
You really shouldn't do this!
You're only strong against
stomach punches, right?
Don't worry. I took two
guys on earlier, too.
I'm sure I can handle these two—
We're here to pay you back, brat!
We heard what you did to our friend!
Who do you think we are, punk?!
Rein, run! You won't get off with
just a stomach punch this time!
It's okay, Nina.
I thought something like this might
happen and prepared the ultimate weapon.
It's tiny!
There's no way! You can't fight with that!
It's tiny! What even is that?!
This has been enchanted
with 10,000 bonus points.
Small doesn't always
mean weak. Right, Nina?
What can you even do
with that tiny sword?!
Hey! Stop pulling on me, Nina!
What was that?
What's his deal?
He's crazy.
He's a monster! Run!
Rein, what did you just do?
I just swung my sword a little.
What are you talking about?
No bystanders got caught in the blast.
I see. That's good.
Yeah, seriously!
You just need to be careful
going forward, Rein.
Master!
I will.
You're a member of the Blue Crystals now.
Our members will help you
and teach you things.
Some of them have been
adventuring for a long time.
That's right. I'm sure you can
learn to use your power well.
I see!
Rein.
You're going to become
an incredible adventurer.
Welcome to the Blue Crystals.
The Blue Crystals covered
the 1,000 gold needed
to repair the street and
buildings you destroyed.
O-One thousand?!
How many years of earnings is that for me?
Don't worry.
You can pay it back while working for me.
Oh, that works!
Nina, got any jobs that pay 1,000 gold?
Rein, you can't do quests
like that without experience.
Nina, we've got that job
we've been ignoring.
Master, I really don't think
Rein's ready for that.
What are you talking about?
Dragon slaying.
Dra...
We received the request two weeks ago.
The client has reached
out to other guilds, too,
but everyone's busy,
so no one's accepted it.
A dragon!
But you're not ready for that.
Most adventurers can't beat a dragon.
Typically, people don't take on dragons
without a few years of experience, so...
Why not take on the dragon? Go for it.
I'll be working in the back.
Please, Master...
The client's waiting, right?
Someone's gotta go.
He's going to slay a dragon while dressed
like he's taking a dog on a walk?
He can't be serious.
Nina, my equipment alone
makes me pretty strong.
This sword has 10,000 bonus points.
These clothes have 3,033 bonus points.
They should be stronger than steel armor.
If you're worried,
try stabbing me with a knife!
I can't do that!
It's true.
It's stronger than steel armor.
Right?
Thanks! Did you see that, Nina?
You should be angry she
hit you with a sword.
By the way, who are you?
I'm Lily. Lily Flambert.
Lily Flambert?
Nina, if you're worried about sending
him by himself, I'll go with him.
But Lily, you...
I'll be fine, Nina.
Have you forgotten that
I'm an S-rank adventurer?
I'm D-rank.
Yeah, I wouldn't bother telling
people about your shitty rank.
Now, let's go. Rein, was it?
Yeah.
Wait, wait! I need to
confer with the master—
Huh? Hey!
This city has changed a lot.
Lily Flambert is a swordsman who became
the youngest S-rank adventurer ever.
Her name is known across the continent.
When she was seven,
she slew five low-level dragons.
When she was twelve, she tamed
and rode a mid-level dragon.
She eventually became powerful enough
to defeat high-level dragons by herself,
but for the past few years,
we've heard nothing of her exploits.
I'd heard rumors about you
being crippled or dead,
but you've been here all along, huh?
I'm right here. You don't need
to tell me my life story.
What's an adventurer like you
doing with the Blue Crystals?
It's a good guild.
That's true. Thanks for
coming with me, Lily.
I don't deserve your thanks.
If you'd gone alone and died,
the guild would be in trouble.
They'd be criticized for sending a total
novice by himself to slay a dragon.
That's why I'm going with you.
I focused on enchanting,
so I've never fought before.
Let me know if you need any enchantments.
That's a magic sword.
Correct.
It's unsigned, but it's a powerful blade
forged using magic techniques.
In that case...
Lily?
I don't need your enchantments.
Let's hurry.
SEVERAL HOURS LATER...
Looks like a mid-level dragon.
A dragon?! Where?!
It's not here.
I can just tell from the
scale of the damage.
Wow, Lily! You're a real adventurer!
I just know from experience.
You'll pick things up while adventuring
whether you like it or not.
Let's hurry!
Where are you going?
To the dragon! Dragon, dragon, go, go!
It's not that way. It's this way.
You know that from experience, too?
Stop shouting about everything!
Lily!
What now?
Soon.
It could appear at any time.
What's wrong, Lily?
Just ignore me.
Go slay the dragon or whatever
it is you want to do.
I can't do that.
If you're not feeling well,
let's leave so we can rest.
Rein, you don't know what I've been
doing these past two years, do you?
I sure don't.
You want to know what I was doing?
I was doing nothing!
Huh? Wh-What are you talking about?
You weren't doing anything?
You defeated low-level dragons at seven,
tamed mid-level dragons at twelve,
and became the youngest S-rank
adventurer ever, right?
You stupid idiot!
Shut up, shut up, shut up!